<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opengl on Portfolio - Thomas Leroy</title>
    <link>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/tags/opengl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opengl on Portfolio - Thomas Leroy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 14:09:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/tags/opengl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teeworlds</title>
      <link>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/teeworlds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 14:09:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/teeworlds/</guid>
      <description>Teeworlds is 2D multiplayer open source game (available on Steam). Its development started around 10 years ago, I joined the main team recently to keep the work going. We released a new version (0.7.2) after years of hiatus. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on remaking the editor from scratch (see below).

Album Progress album of the new editor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burds</title>
      <link>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/burds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 19:48:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/burds/</guid>
      <description>Burds is my first attempt at using machine learning to make AI. This involved implementing feed forward neural networks and reccurrent neural networks from scratch, but also developping a genetic algorithm to train these networks, as well a choosing the right network achitecture. The final result is a mix from several research papers, adding my own contributions to fit the project.


  Demonstration video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0xed</title>
      <link>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/0xed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 21:19:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/0xed/</guid>
      <description>0xed is an hexadecimal editor. View data interpreted as common types such as ASCII, Integer and Float.
Setup as many panels as you want, each with its own color gradient and data type.
Inspect selected byte string with the Inspector panel, Search for any type of data with the search command.
0xed is currently being worked on and thus is not recommended for professional use as of now.

Album Progress album</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resacred</title>
      <link>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/resacred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 15:42:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/resacred/</guid>
      <description>Resacred is a complete remake of Sacred Gold.
First we start by reverse-engineering the game from the executable binary and binary resource files, using tools such as x64dbg, IDA Pro, and 0xed.
We then use that information to build a modern engine suited for the game. In particular, DirectX 7 was used at the time to render the game, we now use an asynchronous OpenGL renderer.
After months of work we can display every map sector, as well as the world overview grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 19:48:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lordsk.github.io/portfolio/post/misc/</guid>
      <description>   
  

  

  
  
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>